"If squashed to death
you wish not to be...
...sing of Svaty Vaclav and his victory."
- Who the hell is Svaty Vaclav?
- Walls are getting closer.
- Oh, boy. Happy place, happy place.
(Sheldon:)Svaty Vaclav was the Duke of Bohemia.
Ten seconds from getting crushed.
(Leonard:)- Nine. Eight.
- What are we supposed to do?
- Seven. Six. Five.
- Wait, wait.
(Sheldon:)Svaty Vaclav is better known
as Good King Wenceslaus...
...from the Christmas carol.
- Never heard of it.
(Howard:)Must be the one Christmas song
not written by a Jewish guy.
- Three. Two.
- Somebody sing the damn song.
(Sheldon:)Good King Wenceslas looked out
On the feast of Stephen
When the snow lay round about
Deep and crisp and even
(Leonard:)Walls are getting slower.
(Sheldon:)Brightly shone the moon that night
Though the frost was cruel
(Sheldon:)When a poor man came in sight
Gath'ring winter fuel
- The walls stop. You're safe.
- That was amazing, Sheldon.
- How'd you know that?
- Simple.
(Sheldon:)I combined a well-known historical fact
about Bohemia...